

Ivica Širanović

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address: Filip II Makedonski 96/11 Bitola

+389 76 626 637

Date of birth: 11.10.1980

Nationality: Croatian

Driving License: B

SKILLS

Management Skills ••••

Comunication ••••

Client Focused •••••

Computer Skills ••••

LANGUAGES

English ••••

Croatian ••••

German •••

HOBBIES

Animation

Drawing

Playing Guitar

PROFILE

Highly skilled Manager and Customer Service Representative with an impressive background specialized in administrative and customer support work. Proven ability to establish and maintain excellent communication and relationships with clients. Dedicated to identifying customer needs and delivering effective solutions to all problems. Excellent time management skills combined with a superior knowledge of the customer service industry. Bilingual, hardworking, and ready to join my next team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

* November 2019 – Present

Dispatcher at Oryx Asistencija, Bitola

Providing roadside assistance that helps distressed motorists get their disabled vehicles back on the road or into garages for repair. Receiving emergency and non-emergency calls and record significant information. Addressing problems and requests by transmitting information or providing solutions. Receiving and dispatching orders for products or deliveries.

* January 2011 - October 2019

Head Manager at Stanben Servis Biznis Centar d.o.o, Bitola

Control, acquisition, accountability, maintenance, utilization and oversight of commercial, industrial or residential real estate.

* January 2002 – December 2010

Various jobs at Various employers

Freelance Graphic & Web Designer, Kitchen Helper, Sales representative, Waiter, Bartender.

EDUCATION

* October 1998 – March 2004, Bitola

Bachelor of science in Graphic Engineering and Graphic Design

Creating visual solutions to comunications problems. Cognitive, cultular, physical, and social factors in planning an executing designs for the target audience.